<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>https://gatsbyjs.github.io/gatsby-starter-blog/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 15:35:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Hello There]]></title><description><![CDATA[At Wisr, we are building a platform that helps students and alumni connect. Emphasis on building. Wisr is an ongoing project – our team is…]]></description><link>https://gatsbyjs.github.io/gatsby-starter-blog//hello-there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsbyjs.github.io/gatsby-starter-blog//hello-there/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 12:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;At Wisr, we are building a platform that helps students and alumni connect. Emphasis on building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wisr is an ongoing project – our team is always constantly thinking about, designing, and building new features. We are collecting feedback from our customers and our users, and are iterating on existing features to make them more intuitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We try to move quickly, and we understand that you are busy. As a Wisr admin it can be hard to keep up. Often when we release an update, your students and alumni will see it before you do – they are the ones using Wisr every day to make meaningful connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Building Wisr is a space where we, the Wisr Product and Engineering teams, can keep you up to date on what we are building. As we release new and important updates to Wisr, we will tell you about it here. Our goal is not just to tell you that we build a new thing, but to explain &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; we built it. When you meet with a Wisr user, maybe in a career services advising session, or at an alumni event, we want to make sure that you know everything there is to know about Wisr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are excited to share some insight into what we are creating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. If you have thoughts, ideas, feedback, questions or just want to chat, you can talk to us any time at &lt;a href=&quot;customerservice@wisr.io&quot;&gt;customerservice@wisr.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>